Guide to the Hoover Institution Archives Photograph Card Catalog
Hoover Institution Archives
- Bellquist, Eric Collection, 248 prints, 16 postcards / 9 envelopes (Box 881092 - 10.A-V)
  - 7 prints depicting Finland, 1930-1940 (Folder G)
    Includes 2 prints of Field Marshall Karl Mannerheim, 1 print of President Lauri Relander, 1 print of President Risto Ryti, 1 print of Foreign Minister Erkko, and 1 print of the Finnish Parliament.
  - 2 prints depicting the League of Nations, 1930 (Folder H)
  - 6 prints (Folder mI)
    Includes 2 prints of the League of Nations, 1 print of President Lauri Relander, 1 print of the Norwegian Parliament, and 1 print of Danish government officials.
- Belodubrovskii, Evgenii Collection, 2 postcards / 1 envelope (Box 92061-Photo file Envelope A)
  2 postcards, depicting St. Petersburg and the village of Bernovo, Russia.
- Bendetsen, Karl R Collection, 1962-1968; 6 albums / 2 album boxes (Box 75100 - 8M.02 fA-B)
  6 albums of photographs depicting Karl R. Bendetsen and others.
- Bennett, Milly Collection, 503 prints / 5 albums / 32 negatives / 186 post cards (Box 82073 - 10.A-V)
- Bergery, Gaston Collection, undated; 27 prints, 1 postcard / 1 envelope (Box 77069 - 10.A-V Envelope mA)
  27 prints depicting Bergery and others (including one of him and Stavisky as children, posing for a grade school class picture); scenes of Chad and the French Alps; a 1931 civilian airplane; sketches of Bergery and of the Chamber of Deputies; 1 postcard of the Berlin Wall.
- Bernardino, Vitaliano Collection, 1954; 1 print / 1 envelope (Box 78026 - 10.A-V)
  1 print depicting a program in a Philippine community school.
- Beyer (Eduard) Collection, July 23, 1927; 30 prints / 1 envelope (Box 30001 - 10.)
  30 prints depicting Emperor Charles I of Austria, king of Hungary visiting the men of the k.u.k. XXV corps at Narajow-Kozowa on the eastern front, including scenes with King Ludwig III of Bavaria and the commandant of the XXV corps.
- Binford (Thomas H.) Collection, 211 prints and 4 negatives / 4 envelopes, 2 albums (Box 74033 - 10. A-V)
  - 70 photos of awards and presentations to Adm. Binford, including several photos of Adm. Binford with Mrs. F.D. Roosevelt, 1940-1954 (Folder A-B)
  - 36 photos of Vice Adm. Binford's tour of Formosa, 1940-1950, including 27 prints of persons of high military and civilian significance, 10 photos of combat action off Okinawa Jima, 1945 (Folder C)
  - 1 photo of Asst. Sect. of the Navy for Air, Artemus L. Gates presenting the Legion of Merit and Silver Star to Adm. Binford, October 26, 1944 (Folder mD)
  - 24 photos of Vice Adm. Binford's naval career, news clippings and memorabilia includes 3 prints of Madame and generalissimo Chiang Kai-Shek, 1 print of General Douglas MacArthur, and 1 print of Japanese Defense Minister Tojo, Circa 1945 (Folder fe)
  - 80 photos of Vice Adm. Binford's naval career, includes news clippings, memorabilia, and photos of General Omar Bradley, 1950-1954 (Folder fF)
- Bisbee (Eleanor) Collection, undated; 7 envelopes / 3 oversize photos (Box 56018 - 10.A-V)
- Blackwelder (Eliot), Collection, 1880-1969; 79 photographs (Box 75081 - 10.A-V)
  52 British official Navy photos (War Office photos), issued in 1942; and 27 leaves of published war photos, which belonged to James T. Merk.
- Bland (Raymond L.) Collection, undated; 138 prints / 3 envelopes (Box 68024 - 10 A-V)
  - 81 photos of relief activities of the Commission for Relief in Belgium and the American Relief Administration in Europe and Russia, undated (Folder A)
    Includes photo of Herbert Hoover and the CRB staff at Rotterdam.
  - 44 photos of wartime scenes in Europe during World War I, undated (Folder B)
    Includes photo of Gen. Paul von Hindenburg.
  - 13 photos of personal and misc. scenes, undated (Folder C)
- Boatner Haydon L. Collection, undated; 71 prints / 2 envelopes (Box 74020 - 10.A.V.)
  - 13 photographs pertaining to the medical training for enlisted men, Burma, 1942 (Folder A)
  - 58 photographs pertaining to the United Nations Prisoner of War Camp, Korean War, 1952 (Folder B)
- Bodine, Thomas Ray Collection, 35 prints / 3 envelopes (Box 82035 - 10.AV)
  - 1 print of adult education class at Manzanar relocation center (by Dorothea Lange); 7 prints of Poston or Gila River relocation center; 7 prints of Puyallup evacuation camp (6 duplicates); 3 prints of Thomas Bodine with colleagues; 1 print of unidentified Japanese-American students, 1941-1946 (Folder A)
  - 4 mounted prints (one by Dorothea Lange) of relocation centers, 1942-1943 (Folder mB)
  - 6 prints (one by Dorothea Lange)of relocation centers, 1942-1944 (Folder mC)
- Bolloten, Burnett Collection, 14 prints, 1 negative / 1 envelope (Box 46002 - 10.A-V Envelope A)
  8 prints of soldiers and civilians in Spain, circa 1936-1939; 2 prints (1 duplicate) and 1 negative of a British political cartoon, circa 1936-1949; 1 print of members of the Fifth Regiment, 1946?; 1 print of Ludwig Renn; 2 prints of Burnett Bolloten, 1987.
- Stephen Miles Bouton Collection, 2 prints, 2 postcards / 1 envelope (Box 83014 - 10.AV Envelope A)
  2 prints and 1 postcard depicting S.M. Bouton, circa 1910s-1950s; and 1 postcard, autographed, depicting Count Luckner, German U-boat captain and explorer, 1926.
- Bowman (Frank O.) Collection, 120 prints/ 2 envelopes (Box XX151 - 8.05)
  - 59 prints depicting US Army Corps of Engineers constructing various bridges in Korea, 1952-1953 (Folder A)
  - 61 prints depicting Libby Bridge-X-Ray Project under construction by US Army Corps of Engineers. Korea, 1952-1953 (Folder mB)
- Brandt, Willy Collection, 1961; 1 print / 1 envelope (Box 61000 - 10.A-V)
  1 print
- Breed, Eugenie Collection, 1933; 1 print / 1 envelope (Box 88050 - 10.A-V Envelope A)
  1 autographed print of Queen Marie of Romania
- Breshkovsky (Catherine) Collection, 31 prints / 5 envelopes (Box XX011 - 9.12)
  - 13 prints of Catherine Breshkovsky. Various dates (Folder A)
  - 1 print of "Dr. Albert", 1920 (Folder B)
  - 8 prints of Prague and Czechoslovakia, 1920 (Folder C)
  - 5 prints of Czar Nicholas II and family, undated (Folder D)
  - 4 prints of Russian towns, 1920 (Folder E)
- Brinton (Jasper T.) Collection, undated; 9 prints (Box m58012 - 10. A-V dr.2)
  9 oversize prints of paintings depicting scenes at the Italian front in World War I.
- Brodie, Donald M. Collection, undated; 4 prints / 1 envelope (Box 82062 - 10.A-V Envelope A)
  1 print of Viscount and Lady Allenby and miscellaneous prints
- Brown, (Andreas) Collection, 1944-45; 11 prints / 1 envelope (Box 71022 - 10.V)
  11 prints depicting visits of Gen. Eisenhower, Gen,. Patton, President Truman, and others to the war zones in France and England. Prints are labeled. Restricted until reclassified by Army censor.
- Brown, Elizabeth Churchill Collection, 18 prints, 2 negatives, 68 postcards/ 2 envelopes (Box 84010 - 10.A-V)
  - 68 postcards, primarily Europe and Middle East, undated (Folder A)
  - 2 prints of Constantine Brown; 2 prints of Elizabeth Brown; 6 prints of the Korean War (one mounted); 1 print each of Generals Wallace M. Green, Payl L. Freeman, Jr. and Arthur G. Trudeau (mounted); 1 print of Adnan Menderes, circa 1958; 1 print anti Khrushchev display, 1959; 1 print of the Advisory Panel for "One Year Later" report prepared by the National Advisory Commission on Civil Disorders, 1968; 2 prints and 2 negatives of Mr. and Mrs. Brown on their travels (South Korea, circa 1957?) (Folder mB)
- Brown, Walter Lyman Collection, 1 album; 2 envelopes/ 5 prints (Box XX383 - 10.AV)
  - Album of photographs depicting relief activities of the American Relief Administration European Children's Fund in Poland, 1920 (Folder fA)
  - Autographed photographs of Herbert Hoover, William B. Poland, President Edvard Benes of Czechoslovakia, and Cardinal D. J. Mercier of Belgium, undated (Folder B)
  - Autographed photograph of President Michael Hainisch of Austria, undated (Folder mC)
- Browne, Elmer H. Stanleigh Collection, 1909-1910; 14 prints, 4 post cards / 1 envelope (Box m81106 - 10.A-V Envelope mA)
  Depicts American soldiers in the Philippine Islands.
- Browne (Louis Edgar) Collection, 76 prints / 12 negatives / 2 envelopes (Box 69033 - 9.17)
  - 3 prints depicting street marches in the Bolshevik revolution in Russia, 1917-21. (Folder A)
  - 73 prints depicting conditions in Turkey at the end of World War I, including photos of Turkish and German prisoners and British officers. Some prints labeled, circa 1919-1920 (Folder B)
- Buchman, Alexander H. Collection, circa 800 prints / 10 envelopes, 14 slides (Box 84075 - 10.A-V)
  - circa 750 contact prints of Leon Trotsky and members of his entourage in Coyoacan, Mexico, circa 1939-1940 (Folder A-C)
  - 12 enlarged prints of Leon Trotsky in Coyoacan, Mexico, circa 1939-1940 (Folder D)
  - 6 enlarged prints of Leon Trotsky with his wife and members of his entourage in Coyoacan, Mexico, circa 1939-1940 (Folder E)
  - 14 enlarged prints of members of the entourage of Leon Trotsky in Coyoacan, Mexico, circa 1939-1940. (Folder F)
  - 3 enlarged prints, including 2 of Diego Rivera in Coyoacan, Mexico and 1 of a painting by Rivera, circa 1939-1940 (Folder G)
  - 40 prints of executions of leftists in China, circa 1927-1932 (Folder H)
  - 14 color slides of Leon Trotsky in Mexico, circa 1939-1940 (Folder Slide Box I)
  - 2 copies of one print and negative depicting the core members of the provisional central committee of the Communist League of China (Trotskyist opposition), 1936 (Folder I)
  - 19 prints depicting members of the Communist League of China, 1923-1982, and atrocities in the Wuhan area, 1929-1930 (Folder J)
    Includes a print of Agnes Smedley with others, 1932 or 1933.
- Buckmaster (Elliott) Collection, undated; 55 prints / 1 envelope (Box 74087 - 10.A-V)
  2 photos of Adm. E. Buckmaster and other officers; 2 misc. photos. 51 photos depicting Commander James H. Mini (Adm. B.'s son-in-law) and others during U.S. Navy Antarctic operations in the Bay of Whales (inlet of Ross Sea), 1947-48, as well as pictures of the U.S.S. Yancy, Merrick, Mount Olympus, Northwind and Edisto.
- Bulhak (Jan) Collection, 1925; 134 photographs / 1 envelope (Box XX093 - 10.A-V)
  134 prints photographed by J. Bulhak depicting various locations in Poland, primarily Warsaw, Vilna, Lwow, and Krakow.
- Bunin Family Collection, undated; 170 prints / 6 envelopes (Box 90075 - 10.A-V)
  - 27 prints depicting Tsar Alexander III, Tsar Nicholas II, and other members of the Romanov family, undated (Folder A)
  - 32 prints depicting members of the Bunin family, landowners, peasants, and scenes of rural life in early twentieth century Russia prior to the Russian Revolution, undated (Folder B)
  - 15 prints depicting Russian military officers from the period of World War I and the Russian Revolution, and the bodies of famine victims during the Russian Revolution, undated (Folder C)
  - 50 prints and postcards depicting historic buildings and landmarks in Russia and various countries of Europe, undated (Folder D)
  - 44 prints of Russian emigres in France between the two world wars, including members of the Bunin family and of the Romanov family, undated (Folder E)
  - 22 prints of members of the right-wing Russian emigre group Mladorosskaia Partiia in France between the two world wars, undated (Folder F)
- Burhans (Robert D.) Collection, undated; 1000 negatives/ 2 manuscript boxes / 875 prints / 11 envelopes (Box XX096 - 9.23)
  - 1000 4"x5" and 35 mm negatives of photos showing the activities of the First Special Service Force and the 474th Infantry during World War II in Europe, undated (Folder 24-25)
  - 4 portrait photos of Major General Robert T. Frederick and others; 45 prints of the 474th Infantry in Normandy and Norway; 107 prints of the 474th Infantry at award formations, parades, and social events; 330 prints of combat scenes involving the 474th Infantry; 98 prints of the First Special Service Force in Italy and Southern France; and 87 unidentified aerial photographs, undated (Folder A-I)
  - 100 aerial photos of Kiska Island (Aleutians), M. La difensa (Italy), M. La Remetanea (Italy), and M. Maggiore (Italy), undated (Folder mJ)
    Includes unidentified photos.
  - 103 prints of the First Special Service Force in Italy, undated (Folder mK)
    Includes 1 print of the 474th Infantry in Norway.
- Burnham (Frederick R.) Collection, 662 prints / 26 envelopes / 142 negatives / 4 envelopes / 61 postcards / 1 envelope / 1 album / 20 prints / 1 sketch / 2 cartoons / 23 slides / 2 boxes (Box 78082 - 10.A-V)
- Burtsev (Vladimir) Collection, 9 prints / 1 envelope (Box 66000 - 10. A-V)
  9 photographs depicting Vladimir L. Burtsev. Includes one print of a bust of Burtsev with the sculptress, taken circa 1909-1910
- Butts, R. Freeman Collection, undated; 25 charts / 1 envelope (Box m 80114-10. A-V Envelope mA)
  Illustrates stages in the history of education
- Byers (Clovis E.) Collection, 7 albums in 4 album boxes, 3 envelopes, 1 oversize folder (Box 64016 - 10.A-V)
  - Clippings relating to the invasion of the Philippines, 1945 (Folder fA)
  - Photographs relating to the military career of Clovis E. Byers in the Pacific and Japan, 1942-1946 (Folder fB)
  - Photographs relating to the military career of Clovis E. Byers in Japan, 1946-1949 (Folder fC)
  - Photographs relating to the military career of Clovis E. Byers in Korea, 1951 (Folder fD)
  - Photographs relating to the military career of Clovis E. Byers in Japan, 1951-1952 (Folder fE)
  - Photographs relating to the military career of Clovis E. Byers in Japan and Europe, 1952-1954 (Box 64016 - 10.A-V, Folder fF)
  - Photographs of Rockhampton, Australia area, 1943 (Folder fG)
  - Photographs relating to the military career of Clovis E. Byers in the Pacific, Japan and Korea, undated (Folder H)
  - 7 photographs of British, German, and Spanish cavalry, ca 1925 (Folder I)
  - 6 oversize photographs of Clovis E. Byers, undated (Folder mJ)
  - 2 oversize prints depicting Clovis E. Byers with other officers of the 4th U.S. Cavalry at Fort McIntosh, Texas, January 1922; and with the Command and General Staff School at Fort Leavenworth, Kansas, 1934 or 1935, including A. C. Wedemeyer, then 1st Lieutenant in the Infantry (Folder mK)
- Caetani, (Galesio) Collection, 1922-1925; 6 photos / 1 envelope (Box 44004 - 10.A-V Envelope m)
  6 photographs depicting the activities of Galesio Caetani as Italian Ambassador to the U.S.
- Caldwell, John K Collection, March, 1917; 1 print / 1 envelope (Box 76009-10.A-V)
  1 print depicting the ceremony deposing the Governor of Vladivostok.
- Canan (Howard V.) Collection, 735 prints/ 3 envelopes, 1 album (Box 74032-10 A-V)
  - 123 photos of H.V. Canan and others at U.S. Military Academy, West Point, 1916-1917 (Folder A)
  - Photos of war damage, pictures of interest and cultural sites in Western Europe, 1919 (Folder B)
  - 32 photos depicting H.V. Canan during his military career and miscellaneous and duplicate photos, undated (Folder C)
  - 191 postwar scenes of Belgium, France and Germany including photos of European tour, 1919; 58 photos of 11th Engineer Regiment in Panama Canal Zone, 1925-1928; 259 photos of Corps of Engineer activities and techniques; Various pictures of vacation and travel (Folder fD)
  - 2 troop and 3 portrait photos, undated (Folder m)
  - 2 troop portrait photos, undated (Folder m*dr. 1)
- Canepa, Andrew M. Collection, undated; 148 prints / 7 envelopes (Box 84034 - 10.A-V)
  - 1 oversize print of President Calvin Coolidge, 1927 (Folder mA)
  - 32 prints of President Calvin Coolidge, his family and his cabinet, 1923-1933 (Folder B)
  - 14 prints of Grace Coolidge, wife of President Calvin Coolidge, 1923-1957 (Folder C)
  - 9 prints of Father James Cox, leader of the Jobless Party and the Blue Shirt Army, 1932 (Folder D)
  - 21 prints of American posters, including 20 prints of World War II posters, 1941-1945, and 1 print of an unemployment census poster, 1937 (Folder E)
  - 48 prints of Father Charles E. Coughlin, 1933-1949, including prints of Coughlin with Congressman William Lemke, Gerald L. K. Smith and Dr. Francis E. Townsend (Folder F-G)
- Cannon, Robert Milchrist Collection, undated; 110 prints / 3 envelopes (Box 77077-10.AV)
  - 6 prints plus one duplicate of 82nd Airborne Div., Ft. Benning GA. 1950 and 22 prints of LT.GEN. Cannon as Commander, 6th Army, 1959-1961 (Folder A)
  - 23 prints of LT. GEN Cannon as Commander, 6th Army, 1959-1961 (Folder B)
  - 16 prints of Sulu Sea Area, Philippine Republic, with LT. GEN Cannon and US Military Advisory Group, 1955 and 33 prints of LT. GEN Cannon as Commander of 6th Army, 1959-1961. One print of Lon Nol at Presidio of San Francisco, 1960, and one print of General Hans Speidel at the Presidio of San Francisco, 1960 (Folder C)
- Caraway (Forrest) Collection, 11 prints / 1 envelope (Box 64009 - 8.39)
  7 prints depicting Caraway during his military career, 1941-1956; 4 prints depicting Heartbreak Ridge, Korea, during the Korean War, 1953. Prints are labeled
- Carman, Charles M. Collection, 1 print / 1 envelope (Box 90090-Photo file Envelope A)
  1 print depicting General William J. Donovan on December 15, 1944, congratulating Lucien E. Lajeunesse for his participation in the Jedburgh Operation carried out by the Office of Strategic Services in France in 1944, involving parachuting operatives behind German lines to effect liaison with local resistance forces.
- Chaisson (John R.) Collection, 9 envelopes / 280 prints (Box 73066-10 A-V)
  - 51 photos of Gen. Chaisson and others in Vietnam, undated (Folder A)
  - 80 Photos of Gen. Chaisson at social and official functions, award presentations and inspections, undated (Folder B-C)
  - 26 photos of Gen. J.R. Chaisson (portraiture), undated (Folder D)
  - 45 photos of J.R. Chaisson and others during World War II and Korean War, undated (Folder E)
  - 10 photos of Gen. Chaisson with important persons, including Gen. William Westmoreland, Amb. Ellsworth Bunker, and J. B. Connally, undated (Folder F)
  - 28 photos of a landing exercise by the 2nd Marine Division, June 1963 (Folder G)
  - 35 photos of J. R. Chaisson and friends near Tsingtao, China, 1948-49 (Folder H)
  - 5 photos of the landing at Peleliu Island, Philippines, September 1944 (Folder I)
- Chan, Ming K. Collection, 1927; 30 prints / 1 box (Box f81107 - 8M.02 Box fA)
  Depicts the aftermath of the communist insurrection in Canton, China.
- Chang, Kia-Ngau Collection, undated (Box 74058 - 10.A-V Envelope A)
  1 print depicting Kia-ngau Chang.
- Chappell (Church A.) Collection, undated; 32 photos / 2 envelopes (Box 74053 - 10.A-V)
  - 27 photos of Captain Chappell's duty in Guam, undated (Folder A)
  - 5 photos of the U.S.S. Wisconsin entering the Auxiliary Dry Dock, undated (Folder B)
- Cherington, Reed B. Collection, undated; 3 albums, 1 envelope (Box 45006 - 10.A-V)
  - 3 albums of photographs relating to the A.E.F. in France during World War I, undated (Folder f)
  - Photographs relating to the A.E.F. in France during World War I, undated (Folder A)
- China - Description and Travel Collection, circa 1928; 6 prints / 1 envelope (Box 71012 - 10.)
  6 prints depicting temples and gardens in Peking and camel trains in the surrounding area. 2 prints are in color. Prints are labeled.
- China - Posters Collection, undated; 11 negatives / 1 envelope (Box XX553 - 10.A-V)
  11 negatives of original posters.
- Chinese National Relief and Rehabilitation Administration Collection, undated; 2229 negatives / 4 manuscript boxes (Box 48024 - 8.29)
  Photographic negatives depicting scenes of daily life in China and activities of the Chinese National Relief and Rehabilitation Administration.
- Christoff (Peter K.) collection, 1931-1956; 3 envelopes (A, B, m*C) (Box 80141 - 10.A-V)
  Depicts social conditions in the Soviet Union, 1931-1956, agricultural work, mobilization of the home front during World War II, the roles of women and children, and postward political leaders.
- Clark (Erik) Collection, June 1925; 41 photos / 1 envelope (Box 74059 - 10.A-V Envelope mA)
  41 photos of the Student's movement in China after the shooting of 21 students in Shanghai.
- Clark (Marmaduke) Collection, 917 photos / 16 negatives /10 envelopes (Box 76032 - 10.A-V)
  - 700 photos depicting the U.S. Army, A.E.F and the YMCA activities in Siberia during the Russian Civil War, 1918-1922 (Folder A-G)
  - 166 photos of scenes in Siberia, Japan, Manchuria and other locations during M. Clark's travels, undated (Folder H-I)
    Included are miscellaneous photos of M. Clark and other individuals.
  - 51 photos depicting scenes in Vladivostok and vicinity during the Russian Civil War, 1918-1922, and the Czechoslovak Legion in Siberia, 1918-1919, undated (Folder J)
- Clarke (Bruce C.) Collection, August 1958; 1 print / 1 envelope (Box 70029 - 9.14)
  1 print of General Clarke.
- Clayton, William Lockhart Collection, circa 1899-circa 1960; 15 photographs, 3 negatives / 1 envelope (Box 88015 - 10.A-V Envelope A)
  15 prints, primarily of William Clayton and Susan Vaughan Clayton.
- Clendenen (Clarence C.) Collection, 468 photos and 61 negatives / 7 envelopes (Box 68022 - 10.A-V)
  - 118 photos concerning Clendenden's attendance to West Point and the Cavalry School, undated (Folder A)
    Includes portraits of his classmates, graduation ceremonies and his participation in many equestrian events.
  - 65 photos and 61 negatives of the Punitive, undated (Folder B1)
  - Expedition to Mexico, including photos of Villa, Obregon and U.S. Infantry, undated (Folder B2)
  - 26 photos of Colonel Clarence C. Clendenen's stay in Japan concerning the 1st Cavalry Division, the International War Crimes Commission and many tourist attractions, undated (Folder C)
  - Album containing 125 photos of Colonel Clarence C. Clendenen's stay in Japan relating to War Crimes Commission and travel photos, undated (Folder Df)
  - 15 photos of Colonel Clendenen in Michigan State College, South Dakota State College, St. John's University and the University of Iowa in which he was the head of the R.O.T.C. programs, undated (Folder E)
  - 13 photos of the Negrito barrios in the Philippines where he was stationed, 1926 (Folder F)
  - 96 miscellaneous personal and military photos, undated (Folder G)
  - 10 miscellaneous photos, undated (Folder Hm)
  - 4 miscellaneous photos, undated (Folder dr.1)
- Code (James A.) Collection, 22 prints and 1 neg. / 1 envelope (Box 72055 - 10 A-V)
  22 photos of James A. Code as military officer and business executive, Brigadier General Carroll Bickelhaupt in 1945, Signal Corps radio equipment, and the opening of the ROTC telegraphic radio station at the University of California by President Sproul in 1937.
- Cofer, (Mrs. Leland E.) Collection, undated; 222 postcards, 81 photos / 5 envelopes (Box 50013 - 10.A-V)
  - 222 World War I postcards from France, the New York Committee for the Fatherless Children of France, and Ireland. Scenes of wartime destruction in France, undated (Folder A)
  - 28 photos of various relief activities during and after World War I, undated (Folder B)
  - 6 photos from World War II depicting the relief activities of Bundles for Britain, undated (Folder C)
  - 42 photos of Mr. and Mrs. Cofer, friends of the Cofers, and other miscellaneous photos, including some from the coronation of King George VI of England, undated (Folder D)
  - 5 miscellaneous photos, undated (Folder mE)
- Comitetul National Roman Collection, 30 prints / 7 envelopes (Box 27) (Box XX(4088875.1))
  - 4 prints depicting Constantin Visoianu, undated (Folder 1)
  - 5 prints depicting Constantin Visoianu and others, including members of the Assembly of Captive European Nations, undated (Folder 2)
  - 6 prints depicting members of the family of Michael, King of Romania, undated (Folder 3)
  - 3 prints depicting CNR representatives in Buenos Aires, 1964 (Folder 4)